{
    "1": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Throw in",
      "answers":[0, "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [1,0,-1,-1]
    },
    "2": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Receiving the ball after kickoff",
      "answers":["aa", "bb", "cd", "dd"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "3": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Free kick with a wall",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "4": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n 1v1 against the goalie",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "5": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n PK",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "6": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Booked",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "7": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Build up play after pressing to the goalie",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "8": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n 1v1 Defending ",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "9": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Receiving a cross in the air without opposition",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    },
    "10": {
      "pregunta": "What you should do in this situation? \n Being sub",
      "answers":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
      "translations":["q", "r", "s", "t"],
      "correct": [3,0]
    }
}